let harryQuestions = [{
        question: "What house does Harry belong to?",
        choices: ["Gryffindor", "Hufflepuff", "Ravenclaw", "Slytherin"],
        correct: "Gryffindor"
    },
    {
        question: "What position does Harry Play in Quidditch?",
        choices: ["Beater", "Seeker", "Keeper", "Chaser"],
        correct: "Seeker"
    },
    {
        question: "What kind of wood is Harry's first wand made out of?",
        choices: ["Oak", "Willow", "Beech", "Holly"],
        correct: "Holly"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Harry's middle name?",
        choices: ["James", "Lupin", "Sirius", "Tom"],
        correct: "James"
    },
    {
        question: "What type of animal does Harry accidentally set free while at the zoo in Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone?",
        choices: ["Lion", "Rat", "Snake", "Spider"],
        correct: "Snake"
    },
    {
        question: "Where was Harry Potter born?",
        choices: ["The Burrow", "Godric's Hollow", "Little Whinging", "Number 12 Grimmauld Place"],
        correct: "Godric's Hollow"
    },
    {
        question: "Who is Harry Potter's Godfather?",
        choices: ["Peter Petigrew", "Remus Lupin", "Sirius Black", "Albus Dumbledore"],
        correct: "Sirius Black"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Harry's owl?",
        choices: ["Fluffy", "Padfort", "Crookshanks", "Hedwig"],
        correct: "Hedwig"
    },
    {
        question: "What fake name does Harry use while attending Bill and Fleur's wedding in disguise in Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows?",
        choices: ["Barny Weasly", "Bert Weasly", "Bagshot Weasly", "Billy Weasly"],
        correct: "Barny Weasly"
    },
    {
        question: "When is Harry's birthday?",
        choices: ["June 31st", "July 31st", "August 31st", "September 31st"],
        correct: "July 31st"
    },

];

let ronQuestions = [{
        question: "What is the name of the Weasley family home?",
        choices: ["Number 12 Grimmauld Place", "Little Whinging", "The Burrow", "Godric's Hollow"],
        correct: "The Burrow"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ron famously afraid of?",
        choices: ["Rats", "Spiders", "Dragons", "Snakes"],
        correct: "Spiders"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ron's middle name?",
        choices: ["Arthur", "Barney", "Bilius", "Arnold"],
        correct: "Bilius"
    },
    {
        question: "What position does Ron play in Quidditch?",
        choices: ["Seeker", "Beater", "Chaser", "Keeper"],
        correct: "Keeper"
    },
    {
        question: "Which Weasley dies during the final battle of Hogwarts?",
        choices: ["Bill", "Fred", "George", "Ron"],
        correct: "Fred"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the first name of Ron's mother Mrs Weasley",
        choices: ["Molly", "Tonks", "Lilly", "Minerva"],
        correct: "Molly"
    },
    {
        question: "What does Ginny say Ron has a tattoo of?",
        choices: ["A chess piece Knight", "A Lion", "A Dragon", "A Pygmy Puff"],
        correct: "A Pygmy Puff"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Ron's favourite Quidditch team?",
        choices: ["Chudley Cannons", "Holyhead Harpies", "Puddlemere United", "Tutshill Tornados"],
        correct: "Chudley Cannons"
    },
    {
        question: "What is the name of Ron's pet owl?",
        choices: ["Fang", "Trevor", "Scabbers", "Pigwidgeon"],
        correct: "Pigwidgeon"
    },
    {
        question: "What was the name of Ron's first girlfriend?",
        choices: ["Luna Lovegood", "Lavender Brown", "Cho Chang", "Padma Patil"],
        correct: "Lavender Brown"
    },

];


let hermioneQuestions = [{
        question: "What is Hermione's first line in the first movie?",
        choices: ["Has anyone seen a toad?", "Oh, are you doing magic?", "You've got dirt on your nose, by the way", "I'm Hermione Granger"],
        correct: "Has anyone seen a toad?"
    },
    {
        question: "What are Hermione's parents?",
        choices: ["Doctors", "Dentists", "Teachers", "Veternarians"],
        correct: "Dentists"
    },
    {
        question: "Who takes Hermione to the Yule Ball",
        choices: ["Harry Potter", "Neville Longbottom", "Fred Weasly", "Viktor Krum"],
        correct: "Viktor Krum"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Hermione's middle name?",
        choices: ["Jean", "Bellatrix", "Lilly", "Lavender"],
        correct: "Jean"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Hermione's cat called?",
        choices: ["Fluffy", "Padfort", "Crookshanks", "Fang"],
        correct: "Crookshanks"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Hermione's patronus?",
        choices: ["Doe", "Otter", "Cat", "Swan"],
        correct: "Otter"
    },
    {
        question: "What is Hermione's wand core?",
        choices: ["Pheonix feather", "Unicorn hair", "Ownl feather", "Dragon heartstring"],
        correct: "Dragon heartstring"
    },
    {
        question: "Why did Hermione miss the lesson on Cheering Charms?",
        choices: ["She was stunned by a Basilisk", "She had turned into a cat after taking polyjuice potion", "Draco's cruel bahaviour made her upset", "She ate too many puking pastels"],
        correct: "Draco's cruel bahaviour made her upset"
    },
    {
        question: "Where did Hermione hold the first meeting for students interest in joining Dumbledore's Army?",
        choices: ["The Hog's Head", "The Leaky Cauldron", "The Shrieking Shack", "The Hogwarts Library"],
        correct: "The Hog's Head"
    },
    {
        question: "What are Hermione's favourite subjects?",
        choices: ["Transfiguration and Charms", "Herbology and Arithmancy", "Transfiguration and Arithmancy", "Arithmancy and Charms"],
        correct: "Arithmancy and Charms"
    },

];

export {
    harryQuestions,
    ronQuestions,
    hermioneQuestions
};